queenbeecoupons.com 2010-12-22

# Privacy Policy : Queen Bee Coupons & Savings

**Queen Bee Coupons respects your privacy.**  
Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of Queen Bee Coupons.

**Credit card details**  
Queen Bee Coupons will never ask for credit card details and request that you do not enter it on any of the forms on QueenBee[coupons.com](http://queenbeecoupons.com/Coupons).

**External Sites**  
Queen Bee Coupons is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

**Cookies**  
A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows Queen Bee Coupons to recognize you each time you visit this site (customization etc.). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and Queen Bee Coupons does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by third party content providers such as news feeds.

**Remember the risks of the Web**  
While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to QueenBee[coupons.com](http://queenbeecoupons.com/Coupons) and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition, other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through QueenBee[coupons.com](http://queenbeecoupons.com/Coupons) have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions. Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.
